{
    "quiz": {
        "sport": {
            "q1": {
                "question": "Which one is correct team name in NBA?",
                "options": [
                    "New York Bulls",
                    "Los Angeles Kings",
                    "Golden State Warriros",
                    "Huston Rocket"
                ],
                "answer": "Huston Rocket"
            }
        },
        "maths": {
            "q1": {
                "question": "5 + 7 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "12",
                    "13"
                ],
                "answer": "12"
            },
            "q2": {
                "question": "12 - 8 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "1",
                    "2",
                    "3",
                    "4"
                ],
                "answer": "4"
            }
            "q3": {
                "question": "3 + 7 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "12",
                    "13"
                ],
                "answer": "10"
            },
            "q4": {
                "question": "4 + 7 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "12",
                    "13"
                ],
                "answer": "11"
            },
            "q5": {
                "question": "2 + 27 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "29",
                    "13"
                ],
                "answer": "29"
            },
            "q6": {
                "question": "5 + 10 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "12",
                    "15"
                ],
                "answer": "15"
            },"q7": {
                "question": "3 - 3 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "0",
                    "11",
                    "12",
                    "13"
                ],
                "answer": "0"
            },
            "q8": {
                "question": "15 + 7 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "32",
                    "13"
                ],
                "answer": "32"
            },"q9": {
                "question": "52 + 7 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "12",
                    "59"
                ],
                "answer": "59"
            },
            "q10": {
                "question": "35 + 7 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "42",
                    "13"
                ],
                "answer": "42"
            },"q11": {
                "question": "1 + 7 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "10",
                    "8",
                    "12",
                    "13"
                ],
                "answer": "8"
            },
            "q12": {
                "question": "3 + 3 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "10",
                    "6",
                    "12",
                    "13"
                ],
                "answer": "6"
            },"q13": {
                "question": "51 + 7 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "12",
                    "58"
                ],
                "answer": "58"
            },"q14": {
                "question": "50 + 7 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "57",
                    "13"
                ],
                "answer": "57"
            },"q1": {
                "question": "53 + 7 = ?",
                "options": [
                    "10",
                    "11",
                    "12",
                    "60"
                ],
                "answer": "60"
            },
        }
    }
}